Is the phone from college
important to you?
Anyway, I'll be there for a while
.  What's your hurry with that
?  Hello, sir, that's it.   We're
leaving the house in five minutes, so
we'll just open the groceries,
okay?
What's up?   Did
you forget to go to the conference? This is for me for
next Pongal.
Exactly. Where is the
bathroom at your house?
Bangalore?
I have enough money to go to Bangalore for the wedding
.
Why don't I go to Bangalore and go
with the groom?
What happened, Bangalore?
Have you changed?  Why do
you change the program so often?  Finally,
tell me where and how far away?   Those who
say to go the Bangalore route wherever they go,
don't you agree with the opposite direction to Bangalore?
I'll tell you, the old professor, that even the old ones can't climb.  [Screaming]
[Laughter]
Hurry up, Iyara.   Okay, I'll get there
somehow.
Why is
this a new program?   I'm
going to the conference and I'm going to come back in one day
.  Shall we come?
Where?
Bangalore is not the only place.  I'll
come,
where is
Bangalore, where is
Bangalore,
Laila, are you going?
Go, you can take a bus or go, you can walk,
okay, what's left is,
coming,
then you haven't come to Bangalore either
[laughter]
Or here, like going to the District Collector's Office, you've organized a
tea contest like this, you're the one who got an interview for a
new job in Bangalore,
sir [laughter]
Tell me a lie, are you growing by watering it?
Yes, it's a new job, you'll
correct me when you say it, new job,
new place [laughter] I'll
forget about you and look after you right away,
yes,
thank you,
my dear. I don't want any job that I forget
.  I
wouldn't have done that if I was in Canada. I'm just going to be a little confused, so come on, man
.
Whatever happens to the little one, dear The Road,
what do you say?  We went to the interview
.  They went there and
asked me a question that I couldn't understand.
What's the question there?  There's no time for even an impact speech, it's just
breathless.
Hey, do you have a shirt?
How did you put all this on? There's a
free one like this, Benin Bermuda
.
What do I do with this?
Oh, this is a plan.
Yes, sir.   As
I was getting into the car, I thought, "Oh
my God, it's going to rain." [Screaming] You told me
at home.  Oh my, Iruyya,
I told her to tell me how she would tell me at home, and not ask where she was going when she left.  Bad things have happened.   Something
bad happened.  The
tax that came and went.   I
know this auto, I've been watching the show.   Are you
angry?  Did
you hit him that hard?
Oh my, which
father-in-law is your father-in-law? I thought it was my father-in-law.
What is it, father-in-law?  Why should I
go to my mother-in-law's house and tell her that I am the
mother-in-law?
Aren't you the only groom?
Listen to the girl and see if he is the
groom.  Yo, did you
say that even if it breaks, which car is yours?
When did I say
that car came, this car driver, I
introduced him, both of them
talked together, where is it? Okay, what's up, what's up?
[Laughter]
He was a little shy, he said, "
Come here, brother, help me, help me, let's do it, let's do it, we've got a picture with the waiter,
oh, the auto is broken, go, go, the car,
what's left, what's left, my friend, I said I'm going to a conference, I put on a mask and I'm going to hang out with my friends, this is a conference, this is a less crowded place, this guy doesn't talk well, even if we were all friends, we would talk well, what's the car?" Oh, the car has gone, the
auto has gone, the driver
has gone to catch it, should I get you another auto,
another auto, why are you going to
Bangalore, your wings,  It's not like they're going to a
conference,
he's in Bangalore,
that's why the time is running out.
Everyone should have gone to the priest and
told him, but why did he leave?
Dad will remember everything and take it away
at that time, that's what
helps me a lot.  I mean, if these people
lied, I
can go to my Vibe and tell you, don't be
confused, it's only you who are confused, I'm
not. Now I've made it clear.
Look, I'm telling you,
why are you coming to my Vibe later? I don't want
a company. You talk to me yourself. Okay, come on,
where did I leave you? No, no, this is it.
Now, if you want to lie to my Vibe, you ca
n't tell me.
Why can't I tell you? You ca
n't tell me. Then how can I tell you? Besides, we've been
separated for a long time, but even if you
tell me, it won't fall on deaf ears.  So if
I want to say something, I have to put four people
together.  Those four are the only ones,
not five. Why don't you add them? My family
broke up, so there are six of them.
I'm the one who brought you together with your family. I won't let you come to
Bangalore, uncle. Don't
worry, you're an old, ready-to-grow-up groom. I wo
n't tell Attukari anything.  Be brave, we are going to a
good cause
.  Hey,
Uncle, there's no room in the car.
This big car doesn't have room for this mother. Don't
worry, I'll
take care of it.  Is there AC in the car or
not?
I'm the only one who's gone.
You're all Tata. I'll
destroy everyone. I'll beat you up. I used to beat you up when I was
young. I'll beat you up
really well. Now if you beat me up, I'll
just wait. [Laughter]
Uncle, you said you were going to your little girl's house. If you tell me
where, I'll drop you off. Are you kidding me? I do
n't want to be with Attukari. Who is it? Is my wife in Bangalore now? Then why did you come all the way to Bangalore just to drop you off? I dropped you off and went beyond Bangalore to deep interior Karnataka. It's a Kannada place. It's a real gundi on the hill. It's near Chikmagalur. It's not there. Yes, I haven't told you yet. It's not there. I
want to ask you.
Where is Attukari? What is
she doing?  It's a pity she's
taking singing classes for singing.
Oh, she sings well. Oh, she sings and dances.
Oh, she sings and dances.
That's just to catch her breath. No,
my father, come and get off. I'll drive to the
gate. I'll get off at the gate. I'll go straight to the hotel. No, I don't want to. I'll
eat at the hotel itself. I've decided to
go to Ponnath and
eat with my hands.  Put it straight,
that's it, don't
turn around,
boy
[Music]
[Music][Singing]
Oh, this is how you brought a cake to my wedding reception.
I can't forget all that after hearing about the wedding. This is my vibe. I can't forget it.
Rami Samatha, make this cake wet.
Maithili herself will be cut.  S Take It
Ready One To Happy Birthday To [Music] You
Happy Birthday To You Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday To
You
Kumba
[Music]
I thought a toy that would suck the key would come out of the cake.
This is also a toy that is a key.   I've
come to give you the key today.
Oh my,
Nagi, we have to be in constant touch from now on
.  You shouldn't leave so much space.   Just like
before,
call us every Sunday.  This is my
new card.   If
there is a chip, the ceramic card is a waste of time. It is time to make it right. Let's
take care of our work.  One two Aquarius Aquarius
Aquarius Aquarius Aquarius Aquarius Aquarius I'll
even kill a girl who doesn't know you, I'll
read your horoscope and
see if it's compatible.
very funny My sexual arousal
is in my head okay
don't worry that's all right sweet mind
in place
never mind thank you
very much for coming on my birthday my name is
Ramachandramurthy RamCM would you please
leave
my name is Marugadhavas nice name
and thank you very much you can go.
Hey, we've come together after so much hardship
.  Oh, you're like Simbla,
then I'll go.  Thank you.  I'm
taking off,
okay, take off, I'm leaving Redjar, what's up, take
off pilot?
Hey,
everyone has come to your
house telling 1000 lies to make you happy on your birthday
.  What does it mean if you just go
?   It
means I don't like any other girl except my grandmother.
Oh, please come in and try this girl. Thank you.
Sorry, sir.   He
looked at your phone number and
said he knew you.
Do you know this person, sir?
Do you know if it's one or not?  Go ahead,
sir.   I did what I
did and then what is the matter?
Oh who is this child? It's like a mistake.
I have never seen you before.
Who are you,
Mani Janakikullam?
That's not a mistake. I have to tell you.
I have
never introduced who this is. This is
Vedanta's father-in-law, that is, his father's
father. This is my father's father.
Greetings, Maragata Valli, Alas,
Magi, Mythili. Your father's father's name is
also Magi, alias Maragata Valli, Alas, Mythili, Magi, Maragata Valli, short, medium, full, in the
company. What are you doing
here? You
said you were going to your daughter's house. What are you doing here?
[Laughter] When
she went out,
they also came halfway and met us.
[Laughter] What happened
next? I don't understand.
During the puja,  Why are there
three or four bears, uncle?
Oh my god, how can you
call me a bear?
I'm going to build a bridge in the middle of the night.
How can you build a bridge with the money given by your relatives? That's the money you
gave me, like a cup of coffee. That's the
two of you, alone. Let's be happy. Let's be
close.
Don't do all that, uncle.
Who do you want? We
came to see each other. We're
old and tired. Let's do our job
together. Let's buy
a vessel for you.
[Laughter]
For the happiness of Raman,
this is how your father-in-law managed it.
That person who sent him is not going to go.
I told him that he will cook some food at the Thingari Math. After that, he ran away and
washed his hands here.
No, he left here and went. The
chit farm that he said was not a thing.  It shouldn't be
.  Thinking about
Ramanagi, by this time he would have become a
tasteful person for our lives, and
Medhuva
Viveki would have started doing so.
The song is over, now all the other things are fine.
[Clearing throat] What's wrong with
me? What's wrong with me? I don't have a name for my mother-in-
law.
What's wrong with my name? The government gazette always changes things. But your mother-in-law is more
beautiful than you?   Let
me tell you something.
Don't tell a crow its own little. That's a wrong proverb.
Okay, tell me something else. When
there's a parrot-like blonde,
okay, let it go.
What's wrong with a monkey-like hothead?
Baby,
ah, the parrot
will repeat what it said, but do you
know what the monkey will do?
[Screaming]
Wing [
Screaming]
Oh wing [Music]
Maji,
wama pa, you
forgot everything, Maki,
now ask what the spelling of Mythili is, what is it, ma gi gi i,
hey silence, silence, is there a good tire, fishy,
brandy, hot, something,
good, cold beer,
where are you going, Lukos?
Hey, he's swearing something bad, is he in a
daze? Look, no
one is in a daze, he's not in a
daze, he's just
evasive.
Two flower vases broke in this Windsor sweet. No, no, no, no,
no,
we're the ones. [Laughter] We'll pay for it. It's an accident. Okay,
what's an accident? Oh, we're sorry,
we've been imagining it
.  What's wrong?
What's wrong?   My
hand fell down and broke.
That's it.  What happened then?   Whatever
you think won't
happen.   I've been saying that I don't like it
[laughter]
.  You pushed her [ __ ] on me
.  I pushed her away,
that's all.
What, it came this far and
hit the ground.
I don't hit him,
he's a monkey.
Hey, you shouldn't be happy.
That's a child. This is a child. Has he put a spell on his mind?
Now that's a problem for someone.
You first try to calm him down.  I'll
go and calm her down.  It's okay
.
Why don't we know how to make peace?
We will convince you better than you.
Who is going after?  Put on your three-piece
suit.  There is no
Sabud 3 or Sabud 4. You
don't need to have a knowledge like the little ones who
are reading. Just read it.
Ingi Pinki Bangi. Father Hat Tanki Tanki Tit Father Creat.
Ingi Pinki
Bangi. So what's wrong? Is it in the tool? This is the end. Bhagavan is shaking because he is praying so hard. Is your Bhagavan giving you everything this week? Hey, hey, hey. [Laughter] Mege, mege, I thought it was a small problem. Is it a big problem?   Did you
put me in?
How quickly, what is the murder song?
[Laughter]
Murder?  You are not a fool,
I am growing by watering.
What's up?  What the hell,
I'm talking like a loser.   If she goes
outside, if she goes
upstairs, if she goes
idiot, look at that, where is the key? It's
here, boy, where is the
pocket? In this pocket, the
hero with the ring, don't go, dog, where is the
file from now on, where is he? He's
not there now, that's it, come here,
I won't pick it up, that's
just a gift, look at that, look at the pulse, what's wrong with it,
what's wrong with him, what's wrong with him, put your hand on his nose, I'm
checking his pulse, don't touch,
fingerprints will come,
why are fingerprints all
scary, Ram Kongu, don't talk, no, it's
Golden Murder Man, we
've come, no, stay, stay, no, there's
only one way for you, go
here, see who's calling, police,
hello [shouting]
hello, I'm
talking to Ramachandra Murthy, everything is
true, what's wrong with
you, everyone, if I go to the police,  We will not cross the river
.  If I don't get caught by the police,
I'll get caught
by my stepmother.
What does it matter which boy is playing with the sheep? I
came here to tell lies to treat my son.  Isn't all this a
punishment from God?  Nothing should happen to him
.
My father-in-law killed me and
buried me in a granite quarry,
right? Should it happen in Bangalore?
This is my state,
everyone's state is the same now, a very bad
state.  Hey, we're all
involved together.  Now we will all
make decisions together.
I think it would be better to go to the police.  Those who think so, please
join me and
raise your hand.
Long live democracy.   Those who
think they should go to the police station,
raise your hand with me.
One, two, three, four, five, majority, don't post that,
I
won't even raise my hand, I'll do it
Look, I
'm a businessman.  I also have
humanity.  I have a vibe
.  And I love her,
okay,
I won't die on a granite quarry.   Let's
go and sing this song to our granite
quarry.
No, I'm a Hindu, she might have a name like Maggie, that's all she's Hindu
.
We will burn her if she doesn't go.  Oh, you sinner, I
told you to burn me. Hey, don't knock on the door, I want to tell you something, don't be shy, don't
say anything,
please come, Samari, don't come in, don't come in, don't come in, don't come in, don't come in, don't come, you're here.
Oh, my God,
there's nothing to do, just
call me. I want
to talk to you on the phone. Idiot, my stomach is not my stomach, my
neck is tied up, I got a
call saying that the flowers are broken.   I
did it myself, I bought it,
put it in the closet and told you to clean it.
We threw it away.  Hey, hey, I'm just sitting there waiting for you to throw the
ball away.
You're the only one who can clean it up.
Everyone else is welcome to come along and clean it up.
Why is the phone unlocked?
What
the hell is this, is it some kind of song from somewhere on the continent?   He
says, "You're a rotten person, you should throw a bag from the floor."   If you
throw the suitcase away,
you're inside it. Get off
now. What are we going to do? Don't
tell me later.
Oh, you're the one who's going to kill me. [Music]
[Music]
Okay, now let's go outside and sing and
make a plan on how to get out.  Even if you sing, be careful.
Hey, don't leave me alone.
You, Maggie, wandered around like a Magpie
before you died.
You are the one who won the Pinky Pangilinan here.
You won't be alive while he's alive.
Yes, he has already committed a murder.   I ca
n't bear to commit another murder.  Ram
Charita Saree, no no no
people, no no, don't change your mind, no
If we put the potion inside that tube,
seven rays will come out.   It
will go straight down.  Let's secretly take it to the car
.  Otherwise, you should
tell the reception.
How is the idea?   Please,
Arseny, please, please,
why don't you leave me alone?
You said you're with me.   It would be
scary to be with a prostitute
.  I'm alone in this, the next time I go
.
Okay, okay.  I'm in charge, let
everything be done as I say.  You
can go if you want to go.
Ready, stay here.
Go to your room, pack all your belongings, and
get ready by the car.
I am
Nanu Aim
Sari.   It's
okay, but it's not fair. It's
you, you're all right,
sir.
Where did you leave it? It's all right, okay
We must use our
brains, okay,
okay.
What are you doing?
Doesn't an ant bite itch?
God must not
forget anything.
He built that building.
Bath?  We forgot the spray.   Is
everything yours? Is
everything done by the old me?
So, you
did it before, so you're doing this
too.  Have
you ever been a bit too old?   There
is a cell phone here.
Bath?  Goodbye, thank you
.
I told him.   Thank you
Singing according to time.
What is it?  I'll ask you later, if you have time.
I am a vegetarian, what will I give up?   I want
to catch the time, I sing the time.   The
pure Brahmin goes and tells him to take the vow.
Oh, Pattu,
hello, greetings, greetings, sir. Tell me,
Kupe, Tantra,
Tantra, Pancha, Tantra, Tantra, Tantra, Tantra, Pancha, Tantra,
Father, Medhu, Paccha, don't tie it, don't tie it,
oh,
[gasping]
[laughter] Hello,
hello, [shouting]
What, it's not coming yet, don't tie it, the guy is going, what, I'm going to
do it. I can
put this here too. Is this the line?   If you
have come,
only the pot has come and you haven't come to sing yet,
oh my, it's like you're stuck in the middle of singing, you
need something to beat that [ __ ], like
this,
oh my [sigh]
I'm shouting softly [laughter] Where did I shout?
You're not shouting in Hindi, are you?
[screaming]
What's wrong with you
?  It has arrived, but it
has arrived twice.
Ya, what did you do when you
fell down and sang?
Okay, get ready, tie it up and go, you'll come back
alive. I don't
know what to say.
What's one thing, Sardarji sang,
okay, okay,
what's up,
Sardarji?
Sadie will be an international film.
Oh, there's a laundry, let's take our
shortcut.  Hey hey hey what are you
doing, you
bastard, I
can't even kill you two here.
[Screaming]
Oh
my god, you
used two or three songs,
but here's one.  You're just
walking around
like this, sir.
Sir, towel,
jatti
mera, langkotta,
jatti mera, let's play the
trick, tantra, tantra,
paccha
[music] trick, tantra   Did you
reconcile the two of us and go away? There
was a fight a while ago. I was playing a game with him and he left.
[Laughter]
What are you laughing at? I'm laughing on
the outside, but I'm crying on the inside. I have to
hide everything. Some people will laugh, some will cry. If you go, let it go.
I
left it. Why do you all
think that? Go, Pudung. Uncle, stay here. She's going to
give you the mattress.
Yes,
I'm going there. When I go, take it and
leave it.
Okay, what's the noise? It's me, it's me,
who am I?   I was
worried that I would be the one leaving late. That's right, let's
leave before the wedding.  She tells me to sit in the back when I go north and you come in front when you come in
front
.
But now the car isn't going back like this, it's the one that drove the car
before.
Don't be afraid to drive the car correctly, he's
done his job.   Don't be
shy.